Welcome to Uwe Manor.
I have to say, you kids must have
a couple of screws loose
to come all the way up into the mountains here.
This mansion's owner is Mr. Uwe Appel.
The Appels family has been involved with
the Republic's government for generations,
and Mr. Uwe is currently the vice-minister
of the Ministry of Health and Welfare.
So, you want jobs to work while
your seminary school is on break?
Well, you have letters of recommendation
from a local politician,
so I trust you're well-versed in etiquette.
Please, don't think of us as students.
We can handle any task you deem fit to assign us.
I'm looking forward to working with you, Ms. Head Maid!
Oh, that sounds far too fancy for me.
Please, just call me Olivia.
By the way...
why's she been glaring at the mirror this whole time?
I look fuckin' ridiculous.
SPY CLASSROOM
Embrace the toll of pain
The scabs that will never fade
That day, a forceful draft snatched it away
Unable to change, I have to leave it behind
Come, outrace your fear
Face the unfamiliar sky and day on your own two feet
And greet the sunrise
Misfortune gave rise to happiness
You saw a guidepost at the end of despair
And now, it's lit with a single flame
Shake off the entangled past
And fight until you find a place your heart can soar
Ah, surviving through each moment
24 Hours Before the Infiltration
The Impossible Mission Lamplight's
been assigned this time around
MISSION: Daughter Dearest II
is to hunt down an Imperial assassin who's
infiltrated the Din Republic's borders.
I'm going to be selecting four
strongest people among you
and taking those and only those members along
with me when I set out for the mission tomorrow.
You've split your duties evenly among you until now,
and I'm aware that doing so has
allowed you all to grow stronger.
However, I apologize, but I can't
take all of you with me this time.
I mean, I guess it makes sense.
He's worried about what'll happen
if he delegates missions to us.
Then again, if he keeps doing 'em solo,
he's gonna hit his breaking point.
In other words, taking along the best four of us...
...is a pretty logical decision, yeah.
Still, it's a bummer.
Feels like it's gonna make things
kind of awkward around here.
Who do you think the four are gonna be?
Well obviously, the team's beautiful leader
Yours Truly is gonna be at the top of the list-
No, but seriously.
Well, Monika's gotta be a shoo-in.
Out of all of us on the Operations squad,
she's our unbeatable star player.
At this rate, you and me are just
gonna end up holding down the fort.
Sure feels that way.
Huh? What're you doin', Sara?
Me and Sybilla are on cooking duty today, remember?
Teach asked me to.
He and Miss Grete are neck-deep
in a strategy meeting right now.
Dang, you don't see that every day.
Usually, Teach always cooks his own food.
I guess the mission's really keepin' him busy.
This is our chance!
I'll grab the poison!
I'll get the restraining wire!
Your teamwork is impressive, but you really
need to think these things over more!
The question is, what's the best way
for the three of us to poison him?
I see I've become an accomplice...
Look, Sara, this is our last chance to get chosen!
Thinking back, he's never gone for
any of the food or drinks we poisoned before.
What if we coated it onto his utensils?
I dunno...
We could make the food super bland,
then poison the condiments!
You really think that'd work?
This looks like it could be interesting.
They sound kind of desperate.
Hmm...
We're just tryin' to poison his food, right?
I feel like we're missing the most obvious option.
I'm listening.
All we gotta do is make super damn tasty.
Sara, I know I've been hiding it, but I'm secretly a klutz.
Uh-huh...
For example, I'm the kind of person who
can know all the right answers on a test,
then get zero points because
I put them all in the wrong boxes.
No kidding.
But here's the difference!
This white-haired chick's the kind of person
who'd take the test the right way
and end up with zero points anyways!
Now listen here, you little shit...
What's the harm in giving it a try?
Let's see what you've got.
Trust me, this'll work.
Heck, if it doesn't, I'll even put on a strip show.
With Sybilla as the star.
Now where the hell do you get off-
Ooh, I'm looking forward to it!
Well, I do at least have a plan.
I-is this...
a recipe?!
I saw Klaus cooking 'em for himself once.
I figured it might come in handy at some point,
so I watched him the whole time through.
If we follow that recipe to the word,
we'll be able to whip up some magnificently tasty grub!
Instead of poisoning the food, we'll use
its magnificent flavor to get his guard down.
That's when we launch our ambush...
...and finish the job with some poisoned tea!
I apologize taking up your time like that.
Thank you, that was magnificent.
It was delicious.
Right? We've got more, so dig in.
Lily, go make 'em some tea.
Aye aye, cap'n!
That sounds wonderful.
If I could be so bold, though,
a little more seasoning would make it taste even better.
Try it. Consider this part of your training.
It's so fuckin' good!
You said it! It's like a whole new dish!
It's not just my mouth.
My whole body is crying out in joy!
This is what happens when you eat too fast.
Th-thanks...
...a million.
Dammit, we followed the recipe to a T.
Why didn't it work?!
Well, I can't say I'm surprised.
You have my condolences.
Don't forget about that strip show you owe us.
I'll bring something to record it with, yo!
I guess that's that.
Looks like we're gonna be on house-sitting duty.
Man, and all I wanted was to go along
and hopefully help out a bit.
I don't usually get bent so out of shape,
Present
but I still can't believe that we were
the four who got picked.
Grete was the one helpin' Klaus come up with the plan,
so that much checks out, but aside from that...
Monika was pissed.
How exactly did Tweedledumb
and Tweedledumber here get chosen
while I, the most competent person here,
ended up having to stay home?
The boss has his reasons.
Now that we've been chosen,
we'll have to work hard enough to make up
for everyone who didn't make the cut.
You're right. This is no time to be sulking
over havin' to wear a maid uniform.
You sure that picking us was the right call?
Would you rather I didn't?
Nah, I'm happy as hell. It's just...
This mission will have a special significance
for you in particular.
That said, I know it's going to be dangerous,
so you don't have to go if you don't want to.
Y'know, for a guy as daring as you,
you sure get cautious in a hurry
when it comes to your teammates.
Well, don't you worry.
I'll make sure we get this mission done!
I owe you a huge one for findin' me in that academy.
Whatever expectations you got for me,
I plan on blowing 'em outta the water!
Wh-what in the world...
You kids are incredible!
Not at all. We were just doing our jobs.
Is our work to your liking?
You'd better believe it is!
Why, you might actually be able
to hold your own against Mr. Uwe!
You honor us.
Our target's an assassin called Corpse.
According to the Foreign Intelligence
Office's investigation,
Corpse's next target is the guy who owns this mansion.
It sounds like he's back.
Our job is to pose as maids so we can protect the guy,
then beat the shit outta Corpse when
the bastard tries to go in for the kill.
So far, everything's goin' golden!
Welcome home, sir.
Who in the blazes are you people?
These are your new maids.
I told you about them this morning, remember?
I thought you might've gone and brought
your little sisters to work or something.
They look like a bunch of wet-behind-the-ear children.
Please, take another look.
See how they all have different color hair than me?
Well, fine.
Olivia, bring it here.
Again with this, sir?
Hurry up and bring it to me already!
You're wasting time!
Two of my close politician friends recently died
under suspicious circumstances.
I've been trying to figure out
where the killer might be lurking...
but now, you've finally shown your faces!
Hmph. So, you're just a bunch of ordinary little girls.
But remember this.
If I see you acting the slightest bit suspiciously,
I won't hesitate to shoot.
This geezer's a nutjob.
You there, with the white hair!
Your test will be to make me dinner.
R-right away, sir.
I apologize for the wait.
I made you beef pot-au-feu with
tendon meat and organic vegetables.
I have to cook all the time as part of my training.
Whipping that up was child's-
Any maid who cooks this poorly
is a waste of space!
Something has felt off about the mansion
ever since we started working here.
The rooms are kept terribly dark, and aside from
the three of us, the only people who live here
are Mr. Uwe himself, his mother, his wife,
Olivia the head maid,
and his live-in personal secretary.
That's only five people.
And the entire place is strangely barren.
From my understanding,
houses belonging to generational members of parliament
are generally much more extravagant.
Damn, you really know your stuff.
To be honest, I actually come
from a politician's family myself.
For real?!
Even compared to the other people I met in those circles,
this mansion's owner seems exceptionally
curmudgeonly.
Given his hatred of wastefulness, he could
very well fire his entire maid staff at any time.
I wasn't expecting this.
This ain't like you.
You should be running circles around that geezer-
The truth is
when I have to talk to men besides the boss,
it gives me a stomachache.
Sorry, what?
I'm terribly sorry.
Don't sweat it.
In that case, I'll handle the old man in your stead.
Oh, Sybilla!
Don't you worry.
This is barely a speed bump.
Let's all put our skills together
and make this mission a success!
MISSION: Daughter Dearest II
Hold it, Silver!
That pillowcase is still perfectly functional!
Throwing it out would be a waste!
Yes, sir!
You too, Red!
I can't take it. You'll have to excuse me.
White, your cooking sucks!
How many times do I have to tell you to stop wasting
ingredients before it gets through to you?!
At the end of the day, our job's
to protect the damn guy, right?
Why don't we just tell him that
we're here as his bodyguards?
That's not an option.
Cunning politician or not, he's still a layman.
He's liable to accidentally leak intel to our foe.
Don't forget that Corpse may already have
gotten close to Mr. Uwe.
I know.
Sara and I are going to continue gathering intel
and providing backup from nearby.
I'm counting on you three
to handle things inside the mansion.
Are you starting to get used to things around here?
I am. Thank you for asking.
Well, I'm turning in.
Thank you for your hard work today.
I need to find some sorta blackmail material
so I can keep the old bastard under control.
He went in for a physical?
I didn't take him for the type.
Is this...
Mr. Uwe specializes in matters regarding welfare policy.
As I understand, he specializes
in exposing the rich and powerful
and advocates for improving
conditions for the impoverished.
What the hell are you doing in here?!
I-I thought it'd be educational...
You're White, judging by your voice?
You shouldn't be skulking around at night like that.
Nose to the grindstone, y'know?
That's the file you were reading?
Why?
No, I won't press you on that.
There's a story I heard, back when I used
to frequent the nation's orphanages.
It must've been eight years ago.
Back then, gangs took advantage
of the postwar chaos to run rampant.
And the Cannibals were the worst of them all.
Over in the capital, they committed
every crime under the sun.
But one day, their ringleader got arrested,
and the gang fell apart.
Do you know how that happened?
Beats me.
The ringleader's daughter secretly tipped the police off.
It was an admirable deed.
Even after all the violent abuse she suffered,
she was still willing to turn the entire gang against her
just to protect her young brother and sister.
The siblings made it safely to an orphanage,
but soon after, the older girl ran off.
Why're you telling me all this?
I just remembered that the daughter
was a gallant girl with white hair.
If she's still alive, she'd be just about your age.
I'll overlook the fact you trespassed in here.
However, all three of you are fired.
But you can't!
I hired you against my better judgement
as a favor to a politician friend,
but I just can't abide the waste of it.
I want you out of here by morning!
At least tell me this!
If you hate waste so much, why not sell this huge house?
It's out in the middle of nowhere.
It's barely worth anything.
Are you sure it's not 'cause being the countryside
make it easier to spot assassins?
I can't afford to die just yet.
The nation's social services still need me.
...and that's the long and short of it.
Sorry. I screwed up.
But I want you to hear me out.
There was a while there where I lived in
an orphanage with my brother and sister.
The place was dead broke,
and for some reason, that just pissed me off.
That's why I decided to become a spy.
I wanted to change the world however I could.
Uwe and I have a lot in common.
Right now, I'm on top of the world.
That punk Teach took my feelings into account.
I wanna rise to the occasion, and I wanna keep Uwe safe.
Please, I'm askin' you to lend me a hand!
It would be my pleasure.
Of course.
How are we supposed to save our jobs, though?
Are we back on the blackmail plan?
I'm gonna cook him a meal that'll blow his socks off
and make him realize what a good maid I am.
Dang, the brute-force approach!
But I like it. It's such a Sybilla plan.
Are you sure about this?
You know that's a state hospital, right?
Yeah.
I need you to send Bernard in through the vents.
I'll steal what I need while he makes a scene.
I'm code name Pandemonium -
and it's time I cleaned 'em out.
Good morning.
Didn't I fire you?
I wanted to thank you for last night before I went.
How insolent.
What do you think's gonna happen?
We did the food prep just like Sybilla asked
while we waited for her to get back.
All we can do now is trust in her.
This is vile!
It's better than last time, but it's still inedible dreck!
Yeah, figures.
What?!
These are the results from that physical you took.
Your red blood cell count is way below average.
It's a telltale symptom of vitamin deficiency.
How did you get your hands on that?!
It's giving you a taste disorder.
On some level, you probably already realized it.
After the Great War, you started
sacrificing everything to economize.
In particular, you went around and gave supplies
to orphanages all around the country.
You even gave 'em the food off your own plate.
So what if I did?
There's a limit to how far you can go!
Your body's not getting the nutrients it needs.
That's what gave you that taste disorder.
You said that the dish I just made
was better than the last one.
That's because I loaded it chock-full of spices.
It was the smell you were reacting to, not the flavor.
When you can't taste anything,
you start preferring food that's heavily seasoned.
At this rate, you're gonna put yourself in an early grave!
You need to hire us.
You can't possibly call that a waste anymore!
I'll make you nutritious food every day,
get you your sense of taste back,
and serve you a meal you can really enjoy!
Little girl...
don't go shooting your mouth off
like you know everything!
Nice, that went well.
At least we managed to save two of the jobs.
Why did you volunteer to quit?
What choice did I have? I mean...
This nation still has scores of people who get nothing
to eat each day but a single scrap of bread.
As someone who works in social welfare,
what kind of example would I be setting to the world
if I went and hired three new maids?
...after he went and said all that, I had to at least
compromise by letting him drop one of us.
Besides, I can't even take the credit for our win.
All I did was copy you.
You didn't just modify the food to suit our tastes,
you seasoned each plate based
on our individual nutritional states.
That's what made 'em taste so damn good, right?
Sure, I got fired, but I'll bounce back.
I can swap to a supporting role and help the mission by-
Was that it?
Huh?
Was Mr. Uwe's only symptom the taste disorder
caused by his malnutrition?
What do you...
Please, take another look.
See how they all have different color hair than me?
You're White, judging by your voice?
No way.
He's got nyctalopia?
Night blindness, as it's often called, is a condition
where one's vision declines dramatically in the dark.
And it's caused...
...by vitamin deficiencies, the same as the taste disorder.
Mr. Uwe does his own driving,
but he should probably give that a rest.
Given the circumstances, he can't possibly
think of hiring a driver as wasteful.
Welcome back, sir.
Your blasted driving is too wasteful.
Can't you steer any more gently?
Wow, rude.
I'll have you know I've got
a perfectly good driver's license.
It's fake, but I've got it.
What was that?
Oh, nothing.
C'mon, watch your step.
Get down!
Over there!
Damn you, killer!
We'll go after him!
What?!
You and the head maid should get inside!
Call the cops, fast!
Magnificent.
The assassin's finally made his move.
Sybilla and Lily, you two should prepare yourselves.
I've been watching the night as it pours on down
Even as it gets closer and closer
(Give it up, give it up)
If I quietly gave you my secret name
I could vanish into the dark to avoid being found
I've forgotten all about those secret tears I shed
Like my cells all got replaced
I'm a different person now
So let's frolic our way through these busy days
I kind of want to talk to you
But everyone is gone
That's not what it means
To make someone a promise
I've been watching the night as it pours on down
Even as it gets closer and closer
(Give it up, give it up)
If I quietly gave you my secret name
I could vanish into the dark to avoid being found
And when we're born again
Flying through a new night sky
We intersect again and again
Standing on level stars
And gazing straight into each other's eyes
I want to give it to you when we meet again